<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bcet</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="description_txt">In Our quest for excellence in education, "OUTSTANDING ENGINEERING INSTITUTE (EAST) conferred on BCET by ABP NEWS National B-School Awards at Taj Lands End, Mumbai on 30th June 2012.</string>
    <string name="dec_txt">It is a matter of pride that BCET was again conferred ABP News Natonal B-School Award at Taj Lands End, Mumbai on 29th June 2013, in the presence of admired delegates and respected dignatories.</string>
    <string name="dec1_txt">NASSCOM facilitate Toppers (among the girls students) of BCET on 24th Feb 2016 which was coordinated by central Training and Placement Department, SKSgi-Durgapur.</string>
    <string name="dec2_txt">Bengal College of Engineering and Technology awarded "OUTSTANDING ENGINEERING INSTITUTE (EAST)" -2014 by CEO of ABP Group along with IIT Roorkee and NIT Rourkela.</string>

    <string name="dec3_txt">Bengal College of Engineering and Technology, Durgapur was set up under the aegis of SKS Educational
            and Social Trust in 2001. The college offers a multitude of under graduate and post graduate degree courses in different
            branches of engineering and management. Proximity of regions premier educational and research institutes like National
            Institute of Technology, Durgapur; Central Mechanical Engineering Research Institute, Durgapur;,
            Indian Institute of Technology, Kharagpur; Indian Statistical Institute, Kolkata; Jadavpur University, Kolkata;
            Indian Institute of Engineering Science and Technology, Howrah; have resulted in vast pool of intellectual capital.
            Today, its infrastructure includes airy classrooms, well-equipped laboratories, safe and secure hostels for boys and girls,
            Multigym, Greenfield playgrounds to name a few. Many high profile Ministers, dignitaries and Academicians of national
            repute have visited and praised the college campus and its infrastructure.Bengal College of Engineering and Technology
            was the National Champions in the years 2008, 2009 and 2010, Runners up in the years 2011, 2012 and 2013 and again
            Regional Champions in the years 2014 and 2015 in the National Entrepreneurship Network (NEN). In 2016 the college
            received the award for Honour Role. These awards ensure a special recognition for the entire Durgapur region in the
            entrepreneurial map of the nation.</string>
    <string name="about_txt">Bengal College of Engineering and Technology, Durgapur was set up under the aegis of SKS Educational
        and Social Trust in 2001. The college offers a multitude of under graduate and post graduate degree courses in different
        branches of engineering and management. Proximity of regions premier educational and research institutes like National
        Institute of Technology, Durgapur; Central Mechanical Engineering Research Institute, Durgapur;, Indian Institute of
        Technology, Kharagpur; Indian Statistical Institute, Kolkata; Jadavpur University, Kolkata; Indian Institute of Engineering
        Science and Technology, Howrah; have resulted in vast pool of intellectual capital. Today, its infrastructure includes
        airy classrooms, well-equipped laboratories, safe and secure hostels for boys and girls, Multigym, Greenfield playgrounds
        to name a few. Many high profile Ministers, dignitaries and Academicians of national repute have visited and praised the
        college campus and its infrastructure.</string>


</resources>
